exports.cn 2006-06-15

# Business Terms - Direct Buy China Products from China Factories, China Manufacturers, China Suppliers..

|  |  |    Your are here: Exports.cn --> Privacy Policy  
---  
|  |  | **_Information Collection and Use:_** |   
---|---|---  
|  China Direct Exports Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others. China Direct Exports Inc. collects information from our users at Registration Form.  |   
|  |  **_Register as Member:_** |   
---|---|---  
|  As Exports.cn specializing in exporting overseas, so we only accept overseas buyers and domestic manufacturers as the members of the website, if an overseas user want to do business with Exports.cn and need more information and better service, the user must first complete the registration form. During registration the user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address), business information (such as business type, business interest). By the information we could contact and serve the user better, for which they have expressed interest.  |   
|  **_Security:_** |   
---|---|---  
|  Website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.   
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just surfing. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users¨ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers¨ information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email: service@Exports.cn 

|   
|  **_Site and Service Updates:_** |   
---|---|---  
|  We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.  |   
|  **_Correction/Updating Personal Information:_** |   
---|---|---  
|  If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that users personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at My Profile page or by email: service@Exports.cn  |   
|  **_Newsletter:_** |   
---|---|---  
|  If an overseas buyer wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we will ask you to register as a member. Of course, the member also could unsubscribe our newsletter at My Profile page or send e-mail to service@exports.cn  |   
|  **_Notification of Changes:_** |   
---|---|---  
|  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you via email. you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  |
